<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>mksscryertower.quest - About</title><link href="https://mksscryertower.quest/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="https://mksscryertower.quest/feeds/about.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>https://mksscryertower.quest/</id><updated>2023-04-26T18:22:00+03:00</updated><entry><title>Klimenko Maxim Sergievich</title><link href="https://mksscryertower.quest/About.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-04-26T18:22:00+03:00</published><updated>2023-04-26T18:22:00+03:00</updated><author><name>Klimenko Maxim Sergievich</name></author><id>tag:mksscryertower.quest,2023-04-26:/About.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p class="first last"&gt;About&lt;/p&gt;
</summary><content type="html">&lt;hr class="docutils" /&gt;
&lt;div class="section" id="klimenko-maxim-sergievich-1"&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Klimenko Maxim Sergievich&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class="reference external" href="mailto:klimenkomaximsergievich&amp;#64;gmail.com"&gt;klimenkomaximsergievich&amp;#64;gmail.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="line-block"&gt;
&lt;div class="line"&gt;IT administrator and GNU/Linux user, ~black~ ( final version of supressive ) person for scientology from my 7 - because I broke the nose of the son of a communist with my foot, and it seems that not one of them, but I don't have much knowledge about hardware and networking on level ~about tele control~ or newer has my own machine without piracy, most of the time I work at the computer or in the fields of other people's actions, all kinds of broken AURAs are complete shit or microwave images of girls who seem to need to be masturbated, it's generally death and horror, or under my primitive sources of electromagnetic noise and I shake from the voices of Scientology=Communism because of that that they are in the microwave range - probably so that I die of hunger without money, but working at a computer is the best thing I have ever done - sometimes there is an opportunity to learn or understand something, because I didn't get lessons or knowlege from Scientology/Army hackers, they come to me, in almost all cases, for blackmail, theft of information and to install a backdoor on my equipment. A self-proclaimed member of the Civil Defense of the USRR ( ! communist,scientologist/andropov/beria fun ), I want and will always know and remember my history and the history of my country.
If you ask me, I don't allow Scientology people and cyber-criminals to use me and my work, but who asks... and by the way, I use Arch Linux.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="line"&gt;I can publish one variant then, after days, remember something and update all the site - because my memory is like a controlled disk.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;ol class="arabic simple"&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The freedom of one ends where the freedom of another begins.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The ends do not justify the means.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Freedom of association and disassociation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;div class="section" id="entrepreneur-or-fop-klimenko-maxim-sergievich"&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Entrepreneur or FOP Klimenko Maxim Sergievich&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="section" id="articles-of-association"&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Articles of Association&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ol class="arabic simple"&gt;
&lt;li&gt;No religion, all religion is slavery and mind controll, only scientific atheism.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Full respect for universal human rights and their implementation to the maximum extent possible, does not take into account religious organizations or other people if they violate them first.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prohibition of human control or programming using technical means and transmission of electromagnetic radiation from scan or records of life activities.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prohibited online piracy/criminals and its support how much as possible. Security reason.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Neuroethics.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Avoiding participation in wars and conflicts, cancel cuthure acts as much as possible. Security reason.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Following the law as much as possible and with honest and fair trial. Security reason.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Not following the will of the society, people or organization of any kind if I (you) do not have freedom, will, and if it does not bring benefit if there is freedom with free my ( your ) will. Security reason.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;No for all scientology/online piracy/Ua army workers and criminals proposes and prohibited work for them when you realy know about them, as much as possible. Security reason.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Follow the principles of the statute of the Interpol organization.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="section" id="author-on-photo"&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Author on photo:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;25.05.1991 in Ukraine/USRR Mirgorod.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img alt="" class="align-left" src="images/ktms.jpg" /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</content><category term="About"></category><category term="About"></category></entry></feed>